(Amy:)You're welcome.
(Leonard:)Also for breaking the head
off the ice swan...
(Leonard:)...so I could hold it
against my pulled groin.
(Amy:)I excel at spatial reasoning,
and I had a hunch...
(Amy:)...that the graceful slope of its neck
would cradle your genitals nicely.
(Leonard:)Well, okay. Again, thank you.
(Amy:)And again, you're welcome.
- Wanna come in, have a cup of tea?
- No, I'm gonna head home.
(Leonard:)Okay, well, good night.
(Leonard:)Good night.
(Penny:)Ames, hi. How was the wedding?
(Amy:)Great. Until I accidentally made
Leonard fall in love with me.
(Penny:)Come in, let's talk.
(Penny:)Do you want a glass of wine?
(Amy:)Wine is one of the reasons
I'm in this fix.
(Amy:)That and this dang pelvis.
(Penny:)Okay, I'm sorry,
what exactly happened?
The inevitable. He was Ionely and
vulnerable from missing his girIfriend.